uniflip.com 2012-06-15

# Privacy for UniFlip flipping Docs

  |  |   
---  
  
|    |   
---|---  

|   
---  
  
On this Web site, we obtain information about you when you actively submit information. You submit information when you register/sign up to become a UniFlip member, or when you participate in any other Web site service (e.g. when you place an order, when you participate in a contest, or when you request information); and when you surf or browse UniFlip’s Web site. We also use cookies and pixel tags to enhance your browsing experience and to collect aggregate traffic information for the purposes of assessing trends and statistics. For more info, please see "Cookies and Pixel Tags" below.   
  
### How we use your personal data  

_General_  
The personal data actively submitted by you on a UniFlip Web site will be used for the purpose(s) for which you have submitted (e.g. execution of your purchase order, participation in a contest, sending you required information, etc).

_Placing an order_   
The data you submit on a UniFlip Web site when you place an order will be used for the execution of your order, and to register you as a member so that we can supply you with the benefits of UniFlip membership. 

_Other uses_   
Furthermore, we may use any information obtained about you via the UniFlip Web sites 

• to personalize your UniFlip Site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you or our consumers in general are most interested; 

• to learn about our customers and tailor specific features or promotions on the UniFlip Sites or the communication with our consumers. 

_Sending information_   
Only if you’ve accepted to receive information, will we use your data to send you such information, by e-mail or otherwise. If you are no longer interested in receiving information, please refer to the header how to remove or modify information you have provided to us.   
  
### Third-party processors  
  
For the purpose of operating our business, third parties (e.g. credit card companies, shipping companies, customer service providers) may process your data; however only to the extent this is necessary to conduct UniFlip business. 

UniFlip has procedures in place to ensure that these third-party companies value your privacy.  
  
### Disclosing of information to outside parties   
  
We do not sell, trade, share, or transfer your personal data to any outside parties other than UniFlip Group Companies and third-party processors, as indicated above.   
  
### Cookies and Pixel Tags   
  
UniFlip’s Web sites use “cookies.” Cookies are pieces of information that the UniFlip server sends to your computer while you are browsing the UniFlip Web site.

Cookies work in combination with content within the Web site itself, to capture and remember information. For instance, cookies are used to remember and process the items in your shopping cart.

We use cookies and pixel tags (pixel tags are tiny graphic images) to track, in aggregate form only, our customer’s site usage and to understand our customer’s preferences (such as country and language choices).

This enables us to provide our customers with services and/or to improve the customer’s site experience. We also use cookies and pixel tags to provide us with aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction, to identify trends and obtain statistics, etc., so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We may contract with third parties to assist us in gathering data; however, they are not permitted to use information collected except to help UniFlip conduct and improve its business.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your personal browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, you won’t have access to many features that make this Web site more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

As cookies are used to track shopping basket items through the order process, it will not be possible to place an order unless cookies are enabled.   
  
### Removing or modifying information previously provided to UniFlip  
  
You have the right to withdraw any consent you’ve given with respect to our use of your personal data.

Furthermore, you have the right to access to your data and to modification or deletion thereof in the event your data as stored by us are incorrect or otherwise unlawful.   
  
### Protecting your information  
  
We use a variety of security measures, including sophisticated encryption and authentication tools to maintain the safety of your personal information.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.   
When you place orders or access your personal information, we require the use of a secure server. All credit card information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above. 

Regardless of these efforts, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We offer the use of a secure server. All credit card information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above. 

Regardless of these efforts, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  
  
### Changes to our privacy policy  
  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changed policy on the UniFlip Web sites. 

You are advised to regularly check whether our privacy policy has changed. This policy was last modified in August 2007. 

### Questions and feedback  
  
We welcome questions, comments, and concerns about privacy.   
You may contact us by clicking on the “Contact Us” link on the home page of this Web site. 

Click here to view UniFlip’s Terms of Use and Copyright Agreement

Best regards

UniFlip 

Return to top
